cheap-r.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

The Privacy & security of your personal information is extremely important to us as the manager and operator of cheap-r.com (referred to as “cheap-r.com” to follow). As a customer, we understand that you put your faith in us to protect your information and ensure to our best ability that it is used in the most appropriate fashion. As such, we strive to ensure the highest degree of compliance of privacy, and invite you to read the Privacy Policy further to better understand how we treat your private information if you choose to use our services online.

Please note that changes in policy may change from time to time and any updates will be posted on the cheap-r.com website.

## a) Privacy of Information

Cheap-r.com is an online service operated and managed by Cheap-R Shopping Network LLC & its assigns. As in all of its transactions, cheap-r.com believes that privacy & trust are an important component of any relationship & as such strive to continue build and retain that trust. cheap-r.com endeavors to make every effort to protect your private information and conducts all interactions with confidentiality and privacy. This Privacy Policy has been drafted and presented to inform you of how cheap-r.com collects, uses, and any disclosure of any personal information that you have chosen to share with us through our website & your shopping experience.

This Privacy Policy is to be considered as part of cheap-r.com’s User Agreement. By using this website, you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, to include this Privacy Policy. By using this website, you are also showing consent to cheap-r.com’s privacy practices, including the usage and disclosure of any personally identifiable information you have shared with cheap-r.com, as described and outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## b) Privacy of Minors

cheap-r.com is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 18 years old, and is not targeted towards Minors in any fashion. By using and transacting on this website, you are warranting & representing that you are 18 years old or older.

## c) Usage Of Cookies

cheap-r.com uses “cookies” to automatically recognize returning users. A cookie is a small file that allows us to customize your shopping experience by applying any notification preferences previously defined as well as display previous search criteria. Any information saved is used directly in the functionality of the website, such as recording display preferences. Please note that advertising partners may also use cookies, over which cheap-r.com has no control or specific knowledge. Advertiser cookies are used to define more customer specific advertising.

You may block or accept cookies through the desired configuration of your browser, enabling or disabling them from being able to save on your hard drive locally.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

It is not necessary to enable cookie to use the cheap-r.com website, though disabling cookies may result in a less than preferable experience & site functionality.

## d) Additional Data Collection

It is possible that cheap-r.com may receive additional data from or about you via ways not specifically outlined or described in this statement. For example, you may contact customer support , or a 3rd party may contact cheap-r.com in regard to an unsatisfactory transaction with you.

## e) Information Usage

Any information that you choose to provide cheap-r.com, through website usage or by other means, is used to provide you with with information and services that you may be interested in, to include potentially email alerts and newsletters. Your information may also be used to contact you in appropriate circumstances, such as to assist you in the usage of & transacting on the website. You may always choose to provide information or not, understanding that this will affect our ability to assist you and in providing specific services. 

You may opt-out of receiving future mailings and communications at any time.

## f) Personal Data Transfer

Be assured that your personal data will be passed on potentially only in anonymous form. cheap-r.com does not publish any of your personal and confidential information without your express consent, or unless legally obliged by law.

## g) Protection From Web Crawlers And Spam

cheap-r.com guarantees that it will only use your email address with your express permission and consent for the uses described and outlined in the conditions of use. We will not sell your personal information, to include your email address, to any 3rd parties and will endeavor to protect your email address from capture by web crawlers and spiders to the full extent within our capabilities. If you think your email address has been compromised or captured in this fashion, please contact or technical support team immediately.

## h) Privacy Guidelines Changes

Any changes to the privacy guidelines will be posted on the cheap-r.com website.
